Jhal
Hello Hello Friends, setting this up from the beginning,
I am Sumit Pandariya,
thank you very much for watching this video.
Today our topic is Nabi
Health Insurance,
but normally it is very important, till the time it is
said that the water goes above the head, then I
review a product or a company, I never
take the name of the company, so here I will
try to pay a little attention to this Nabi, which is a San Francisco product, now see,
subscribe to us, Ravan, just earlier I messaged
because whenever I say something, it remains
less on the topic, the time to speak is also less,
so finally tell me on which topic should
we talk, then his message came that
Candy Review Naveen Sureon Servicing should start,
so see what is this policy, so I will
not talk much about the product here, I will talk about one such thing
that when a company launches today, then whether it has
USP or not,
what is its unique selling point, like we have
photos of many off-commerce companies in India
Or nowadays you have many apps in which you can
order things sitting at home or
pack them in food items,
why do 99.99% people go for it, one thing gets settled, an even more
important thing is available at a cheaper rate,
alarm is set, so in today's date if you
should buy gold, if you go to buy gold, the
rate of gold is
₹4000, then when you go to buy it, you will
get the same in Ahmedabad also, now you will get it in Mumbai, you will get it in Kolkata, at the
most there can be a
difference of ₹100, 200, ₹3000,
I know Eminem's industry is food, but there is a
bigger difference in Night Fall, the
item which is being delivered to you is a
simple app, now the second thing is that
when we buy any other mobile, whether
you buy it online from mobile or
from a shop near your home, then there is a difference of ₹2500,
but the delivery of the product is
illegal, when we talk about health insurance, it is a
health insurance policy, if
you are admitted in the hospital, then
under this you will get  The insurance company will pay the expenses incurred, it is a
simple side product, it is a
product of the basic service industry, and the
rest that we talked about, we talked about gold
or a mobile, what happens on the basic, it is a
service industry, here
transactions worth lakhs of rupees are taking place, here
you have a product, your bike, here you
pay a few thousand from your pocket and you will get the
company to buy it, but see,
most of the main transactions that are taking place are on
trust papers, I am
not speaking ill here, I do not speak well
of any company, I believe that
talk very clearly because in this policy,
when we are buying a policy from any insurance company, there is some
thing or the other in the
policy, when you have to buy a policy, it comes to
your mind that am
I buying the right product, secondly, we are
talking about one thing, then in the process of buying it, am I making
any mistake that tomorrow the
company says that you did not tell this, otherwise the policy will be fine, to
buy the policy properly, we have to consult a doctor
only, and the third thing is that your policy does
not come to you correctly, it tells him
What steps can you take to cross check whether you have got it or
not,
fourthly, now that you have got the right policy, it will come in handy someday or the other, so
when the claim comes, does it happen
in life that
we immediately go to the hospital and
our work is done, no, nothing like this happens in real life,
if a company says that it will pay the
claim in 30 minutes, 1 hour or 2 hours, then it does not happen like this in real life, it is not like that,
companies do not give, there are
many steps involved in it, if
you send a child to someone's tuition centre, then
they say that
we have a 98% result, then
your child will get it, it does not come,
your child has the capability, there should be a
good teacher there, after that there are many factors which we are talking about,
but you go there thinking that
maybe there is a right environment, similarly when you go to the health
insurance policy, it will
not come in handy someday or the other, four-five
things are involved in it, when you
bought the policy, were you told everything or did you understand it, that is important,
secretly in the policy  Whether
you have read the terms and conditions properly or not, the company
rejects the claim on the basis of space, saying that
this thing is not known at all. Thirdly, when you are
going to the hospital at the time of treatment and
that person makes a mistake, the
hospital staff is also not God,
someone or the other makes a mistake or
when we go to the hospital and the company asks
any question, then we have to reply to it.
If that thing has to be handled properly,
your investigation is going on, then
what things have to be kept in mind at that time, whether there is
any mistake on your part, all these
money transactions are going on in which the
hospital is made to talk to the insurance company,
many times you talk about that investment, a
lot of money transactions are
going on, we
need guidance in this, when you talk about a company like
Digit Insurance, right now,
innovative products are coming, it is a
very good thing in the market, but
if I have to talk about the policy, I
already have thirty companies in India with them.
If I write a little bit, if I
live in a village, then the price of the office is sold in meters,
friends, it will be visible in kilometers,
if I live in a tribal area or
in a big city, then all the companies there will set up
their offices for backup.
Now
what work is done in these offices, firstly, there is a sales feeling at 99%, that is why
claims are not settled there, any
sales officer settles the claim, but sometimes
we have to talk to the company for something,
now if I have an issue in my throat, then
I can go there and fight, I can talk
that brother, why am I born in this street,
when I enter someone's temperature, maybe
he will help me or
I will get the correct information, now
how many people are there in India who are doctors and
how many people are there in Reliance and how many
people are there who are highly educated, who can
read the terms and conditions of that company very easily, but the percentage of such people is
very less that today a
new company has come, I open such a place that
What is the USP of that company, is there any
strength in its meeting, the product does
not seem to me to be very hybrid, you
speak, cheap goods are being sold, why is there no
office opened,
what is the intermediary in between, there is no branch manager, so
these are the people for service or
these collars are cut, when you have to make your
renewal, your payment, you have to make the online
last date today and if you cannot make the payment online, then can you make a
cheque deposit, day
deposit, right to service, this is a service
industry, which has a lot of work for the passengers, I will
make it, I will help you in getting inside it,
many times, when I am
talking about a service industry, the question here is
what is the setup for providing the service on the spot, now this news which is needed, in this
we will also talk
that many people are being
cheated by the company and they are being suspended,
that you had taken your loan by going here, so
when you
connect potatoes with technology, then mobiles get hacked, so does
every person in India, when he is
talking about online policy, does he have to do every single
thing  You have a proper understanding of this. Many
insurance agents do not have any knowledge about the
policy, then what about the normal consumer,
how much better knowledge can they have, so
my recommendation is normally I do not say
that do not buy a policy, my
opinion is that I will buy a self-service because
if I have to talk about a policy for myself today, then
I would talk about the 30 step
companies of India, some companies are 20 years old,
some companies are 5 years old, the
patience of the top ten companies among these,
why are they in the hurry to save only Rs. 1000-2000, when you
find a policy with a charge in the market, greed comes in the mind, the
same is the service industry,
if any company charges more, then
it has also created a service network, if some
Chinese company comes, then Urmila will
give you Rs. 10,000, they will take a loan of Rs. 6000, Jethalal will
come for service tomorrow, everything is done
online, no, nothing
happens online, here you need a guide in step 4,
then the process of selling the policy
If the company
animates in that, saying that we have done an amazing job
with you, where is the transparency? If someone from a
company comes and asks me, I will
tell you 36 ways that if you have to sell a policy online, then
how
can you see it properly so that the consumer gets the information, I am
sending such insurance agents to someone,
these big portals can do
thousands of times better work than the big companies, the
only problem is the intention,
torch light, so what is the basic requirement of a consumer, I do
n't have to buy a policy, I have to get a clean tomorrow, so
for a claim, if I have
723 online bank
policies of 30 companies today, why would I go there,
I don't have to hug anyone tomorrow, I have to talk to anyone,
if I go to the office, then my confidence
is built by spending two, three, four, two, three or it will remain, if I am getting
confidence from the makers, if I am getting a
backup, then definitely I will go
for it, there are 30 companies in India, I do
not do this, there is nothing like all these things are useless,
but on various  Parameters
in the industry today, if someone wants to
buy a petrol car, stop that and buy a
Honda car, it seems useless, it wants a diesel,
we know that
nobody makes a diesel engine like Twitter, we want a tube top, in
today's date in the industry, in all other
things, this Nikah compromise is all fine,
you can get sugar there too, so
definitely look for it, similarly in insurance, money is
not what matters, in this, claim for chilli peas, will
I get a claim tomorrow,
how much will I get, will I get it, it is all a matter of discussion,
first of all this is the question,
today I live in a village,
I do some small work in a village
and I do not have the budget,
who told me online, buy a policy, if the
claim comes tomorrow, then are we so
intelligent, are
all the people in our family so intelligent that
we can just call the call centre and get it done,
talk about reality,
talk practically, India still lives in villages,
small towns, find out their
need there, then send them, do urgent work,
they should do better work or the online people have less
status  They are not doing well, it is a simple thing, what
I want is that my recording should at
least be constructive work with 500 companies, I have
seen it for 5 years, it is a 20 year old
company, why would I go after a new company
where the only proposal to go is
that they are getting subsidy on 2,000, otherwise
look, you also have your own experience in the world,
you have also seen the world that
expensive one time cheap on Sunday, if the products of any
company, be it this company or any other company, are
good, amazingly
competitive, you cannot say that you are better on rent, just by pricing, you
cannot say that you are better on rent, it is a
reality, from my side, I do
not comment on this policy to anyone,
I do not say that any of these companies are bad, there is nothing like that,
when I have better choices,
right steps with which companies, then it is a simple
thing, why would I be able to stay, so
now the point comes here that
what is the relation in buying a policy, you should comfortably go
inside and think for yourself, do
not go by what I say, do not
believe what I say, use your own mind,
here  But we are talking about the service
industry,
guidance is most important in the service industry, from
policy talks to service
tax at the Centre, we need guidance, so I am
not talking about my profession here, if
I am a normal consumer, if I
do a polypack today, then I will
take the top five companies in India, the top five companies in it will be those
which have an established system,
process, transparency, their call
centers are working well,
we are getting their local support, I will
go here only, why, in today's date I do the best
insurance work, but I am also a
consumer, I have a mind, I have a
wife, I have children, I have to
handle my family, so can
they do that by depending on the call center,
only we are the ones, it should be said that if
you ever try, you have
bought an item online and there is an issue in it,
then you remember that day
when you called the call center by mailing them, but
still you do not
get the service, then you will know the reality,
selling is very easy, service is the biggest problem  It is a
difficult task. To provide service responsibly, the
company has to open offices and
you will have to take steps. Everything has become
online, then only God is the master. So,
I tried to give a little professional advice
and if you want to know a little about your personal life, then from
my side I would
highly recommend this policy to anyone.
Yes, if someone who does not have money will
definitely like Maithili, then it is
okay, but it exists. So,
now
if we ignore the service just for the sake of saving fifty percent money,
and if we do
not have much understanding, then I will
not talk much about the product. Let me talk to a general person,
whatever color is close to ground reality.
Thank you very much for taking the time to watch this video. If
you liked anything in this video, then you
can like it, share it, you will
like it, sorry, only that
promotes it. Our website has become
quite popular, you can also go there and
talk about our packages. Anything
best to give you a package online, you
can do it only at this time on our website.  If you have any
suggestion of your kind, then you
can WhatsApp us or mail us on this number and if someone
likes it a little bit, then you can subscribe to the channel,
let me thank you again
for watching the video, thank you very much, Vande Mataram for